you know, Ted Turner, Warren Buffett. Listen to me. I
don't care how much money you make. You only get
24 hours in a day. In a difference between over
and the person that's broke is over uses her 24
hours wisely. That's it to me. That's it. You get
24. I don't care. You broke, you grew up, bro.
I don't care if you grew up rich. I don't
care if you're in college, you're not in college. You
only get 24 hours and I blew up.
I went from being a high school dropout to selling
6,000 books in less than six months. What happened? My
24 hours. I was like, okay. Are you got to
get a grip on your 24 hours? Because you bought
to be broke for the rest of your life and
it just all I need you to do. For me.
I can tell you all about your life. If you
just write down your 24-hour schedule for me. You let
me look at it. I can tell you where you
going to be in five years. I can tell you
when you going to continue, I could tell you when
you going to be 20 years, if you keep that
schedule.